https://www.farran.com/privacy-policy

We use cookies to improve your experience on this website.
Read More
Allow Cookies
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This statement relates to the privacy practices of Farran Technology.
Our Committment to Privacy
Farran Technology fully respects your right to privacy and actively seeks to preserve the privacy rights of those who share personal information with the company.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Farran Technology does not collect any personal information about you on our website apart from information which you volunteer (for example by using our online contact form). Any personal information which you volunteer to Farran Technology in connection with our website will be treated in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1988 and Data Protection (Amendment) Act 2003.
Accordingly, Farran Technology shall only process such information in line with the purpose for which you provided it to the extent necessary to provide you with the information or service you require. Farran Technology shall not disclose your information to third parties unless you are specifically informed otherwise or we require a third party to process the information on our behalf (in which case Farran Technology requires these third parties to comply with its instructions and we require that they do not use your personal information for their own business purposes, unless you have explicitly consented to the use of your personal information in this way).
Revisions to Privacy Statement
Farran Technology may revise this privacy statement from time to time. Changes to this privacy statement will be posted here so you should periodically check this page to review the most recent statement. If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of Farran Technology should be referred to Tom Scanlon at the following email address: tscanlon@farran.com
